theredpin.com 2017-02-16

# TheRedPin - Privacy Policy

In order to take advantage of TheRedPin, Brokerage's services, including project enquiry and new condo unit purchase, you must complete a registration form. Here at the TheRedPin, Brokerage we value individuals as well as their right to privacy. We strive to protect all of the personal information that is shared with us through the website and are fully committed to keep your personal information, including name, telephone number, email address etc. confidential.

This Privacy Policy is to ensure that this goal is met properly. Please note that "personal information" refer to any detail that identify you, the user, as an individual. By visiting TheRedPin, Brokerage you agree to abide by this privacy policy as well:

  * We only collect , store, use, and retain personal information which is absolutely necessary in order to allow us to assist you with your enquiry and/or to make your real estate transaction possible
  * You can refrain from submitting the required information at your discretion, however that would likely prevent us from providing complete service with regards to new condominiums in Toronto and GTA
  * We will never share your personal information (unless you explicitly indicate otherwise) to any third party person or company
  * We will abide by and act according to Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act in Canada
  * Only employees who directly work on the appropriate departments and accounts have access to the personal information submitted. All of our employees are aware of our Privacy Policy and strive to abide by it
  * We also collect "traffic data" from your browser which includes your IP address. This allows us to monitor and maintain our servers and analyze trends and user behaviour in order to enhance our customer service
  * We are committed to maintaining acceptable levels of physical, and technical security with regards to our information storage facilities in order to prevent unauthorized access, misuse, loss, disclosure, or modification of personal information submitted to us
  * Please note that this policy only applies to entities we own and control as well as employees we manage. As a result it excludes third party entities and individuals that we do not employ and/or manage
  * TheRedPin, Brokerage reserves the right to modify the terms stated in this Privacy Policy without notice. Any information collected will be subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy at the time the information is collected.
  * If you are a foreign user and/or purchaser, please note that TheRedPin, Brokerage users are subject to Canadian laws and you are protected under the Privacy Policy. We will not share your information with anyone outside the organization without your explicit request
  * This Privacy Policy applies to all pages under TheRedPin, Brokerage domain including TheRedPin Pulse Blog and TheRedPin Brokerage
  * We will attempt to collect user information only if you are 13 years or older. Overall, you must be 13 years or older to use TheRedPin, Brokerage. If such information is indeed collected we will remove it promptly
  * TheRedPin, Brokerage may occasionally contact (email, phone, sms) you with regards to information about our services, real estate industry overall, and/or new condo opportunities that is appropriate to you as a TheRedPin, Brokerage user. If you choose to unsubscribe from these messages please email us at info [at] TheRedPin with your request
  * The information stated here is believed to be completely accurate, though it may not be so. If any part of the agreement applies to you as TheRedPin, Brokerage user, you are required to email us at info [at] TheRedPin in order to verify the terms
  * If you have any concerns or questions with regards to this Privacy Policy please email us at info [at] TheRedPin with your enquiry. You will be contacted promptly

We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online Sites and/or Services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage history, and other similar information. 

The third party analytics companies who collect information on TheRedPin, Brokerage and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies. 

You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the ](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)[Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
